magpul.com 2013-06-30

# Magpul Industries Ecommerce

**OUR COMMITMENT to PRIVACY**

The Magpul Industries Corp. Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in dealing with our customers. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**   
When you visit our Web Site you may provide us with two types of information- personal information you knowingly choose to disclose and Web Site use information as you browse our Web Site: 

**– Personal Information You Choose to Provide**  
If you choose to purchase products from us, you will need to give us personal information. For example, you may need to provide the following information: 

  * Name  

  * Billing address
  * Shipping address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Credit card number

**– Web Site Use Information**  
Similar to other commercial web sites, our Web Site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" and web server logs to collect information about how our Web Site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, and time spent at our Web Site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. This information helps us to constantly improve our Web Site and better serve our customers.   
We also use cookies to record individual visitors' session information including items that visitors add to their shopping carts. 

**HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US?**   
We request information that we believe will help us serve you better. For instance, your phone number allows us to call regarding shipping issues and your e-mail address allows us to send you order and shipping confirmations.  
If you supply us with your email address you may receive periodic notices from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such notices, please let us know by sending us an e-mail at [orders@magpul.com](mailto:orders@magpul.com) or by calling us at 1-877-4MAGPUL. 

**HOW DO WE SECURE INFORMATION TRANSMISSIONS?**   
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving credit card data exchanged with our Web Site and adopt internal procedures to safeguard personal information within our system.   
Other email that you may send to us may not be secure and, for that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information to us through an unsecured email.   
Despite our commitment to data security, we cannot guarantee that our systems or the Internet will always be secure. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. 

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**   
We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure. Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information and we will never share any information collected with any outside entity except as required by law.
